[{"answer": " She's very attractive", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Just okay", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "She's all right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "She's not beautiful", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I think she's beautiful", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm not gonna ask her out", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He said what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "\"The hell with them", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " He was pretty emphatic", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Pounded", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah. Yeah, we've been intimate", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, no. I don't wanna say it out loud. Kills the spontaneity. You know, my friend, he never rehearsed.  'my friend, go 'head, do it. my friend picks up the phone, while my friend prepares himself", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Talk to him", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What happened? What'd he say?  What's going on here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Get together!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Did you enjoy your poisson", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " And how was yours", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Come on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What am I gonna say", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How you gonna pay? You don't even have a wallet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What're you gonna do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " There's a my friend to see you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, it's a good looking piece of meat.  Wow, this is some place. A duplex, huh?  Look at this, you got stairs in an apartment. All my life, I dreamed about having steps in an apartment. Even one step. Sunken living room. Although, one step is really not all that sunken.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, that's a fair question. It is, uhm...  my friend, yeah.  my friend's a friend of mine.  He uh, he gave it to me. Unbelievable how many addresses of people this guy has. my friend closes the door", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Thank you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Okay. my friend sits and the leather of the chair makes a series of embarrassing rumbles and squeaks, with more of the same as he emulates Dr that place's crossed legs sitting position", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Could I offer you something to drink. Uhm, coffee? Anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't think we have that", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Wow. You really have a terrible voice", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Uhh, I don't think so", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Wha...? What are you talking about? What'd he say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You talked about a lot of things? Well..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I woulda taken you to the airport", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Neither do I.  Yeah", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What ever happened with that place and the deal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He turned it down", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Hey, my friend.  Hey, my friend. How are you? He approaches my friend for a greeting", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Alright, we're coming down", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Dad, before we go, I got a little something for you. my friend fetches a small package from the kitchen drawer and offers it to my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Take care now. So long. my friend and my friend walk away to cross the street back to the apartment. They speak quietly, so's my friend and my friend don't overhear", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Oh, he took it. I put four hundred dollars in the new wallet", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You're kidding", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Watch.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Man, would I like to see the look on his face. my friend gives a final wave to his parents. They wave back", "qsentId": 46}]